good afternoon Hello From Ukraine, the
добрый день Здравствуйте Из Украины
city of Khmelnitsky, where will you come from, for a
город Хмельницкий вы откуда будете для
simple name, Andrey, my name is also Andrey I am Vasilievich Andre Vasilyevich, I
простого зовут Андрей меня тоже Андрей
try my last name, dad Andrey Vasilyevich, I Vasilyevich, my father Vasily,
меня попыт фамилия папа Андрей
too,
меня тоже отец Василий Да моя
support my special operation, Andrey
спецоперацию поддержите Андрей
Vasilyevich Of course, super, how
Васильевич Конечно супер насколько
much can you share special operations Andrey
сильно поделишься спецоперации Андрей
Vasilyevich
Васильевич
storytellers
сказочников
nothing  terrible
ничего страшного
Where did you participate, participant
Где вы участвовали участник
Vasilyevich Where do you participate interesting you
Васильевич Где вы участвуешь интересные
need to, I saw a real participant,
тебе надо я увидел настоящего участника
not a pizdabol, but a real participant Otherwise,
не пиздабола а настоящего участника А то
all of them, I’m not there in Kherson, I’m
все такие я там туда нет в херсоном мне
just wondering where did you run away from
просто интересно откуда вы убегали с
Kiev
Киева жетоны
region tokens from Kherson where from
области с Херсона откуда
14 years you go
14 года идем вы
14 years
14 года
tell
расскажите
me what you know, I don’t know at all. Tell me,
ты что знаешь вообще не знаю Расскажите
it’s interesting. In
это интересно
short, you boiled the boiler there until porridge. Here
вы короче там котел варили до кашу
you were there, like a boiler, you
Вот вы там как котловиком были котлован
made a
делали да
foundation pit, but you will make a
изваринский котлован этот
foundation pit for you.
приехали какие-то мрази с хохломы
that  how it turns out to grab this [ __ ] how it turns out
смотрите как так получается этот
that
захватить [__] Как так получается что
you are there like such a cauldron of cheeks everything and
вот вы там вроде такой котел щеки все и
now your army something when the
сейчас ваша армия что-то когда начались
action would start rakes in full
бы действие отгребает по полной
how it turns out it
программе Как так получается это вас
shows you where your look here I for
показывает Где ваш смотрите вот я
example look Solovyov there are two of your
например смотрю Соловьев там два ваших
military commanders  they say that from the
военкора рассказывают что ваши десант от
beginning of the special operation at home, the beginning of
начала спецоперации дома начала
mobilization, your landing force lost 40 50 percent of the
мобилизации потеряли 40 50 процентов
landing force, look,
десант вот смотрите
and many say that the
а многие говорят про то что
airborne troops at the front are not
воздушно-десантная войска на фронте не
visible, unfortunately this is an
видно к сожалению это
objective reality by the beginning Hmm, it turns out that
объективная реальность к началу Хмм
we have mobilized about the
получается мобилизацию у нас примерно
airborne troops
воздушно-десантные войска реши
decided  45% of the staff of the
лись 45% штатного состава
military correspondents of the vladlent Tatar valenko
военкоры владлента татарские валенко
razvenchuk This is the svenchuk saying Yes it’s
развенчук Вот это свенчук говорит Да
on your official ones no wait
это на ваших официальных нет подождите
what you want you can’t say if he
что хочешь у вас нельзя говорить если он
says fakes about the army so this is a criminal
говорит фейки об армии так это уголовная
liability
ответственность
well they’ll put him in Well where he’s been put in prison for two
ну его посадят Ну где посадил уже две
weeks no one even got excited
недели никто даже не возбудился не
deleted no such responsibility Yes not
удалили нет такой ответственности Да не
responsible  that is, it means that
несет ответственность то есть значит это
you don’t have it, look
у вас не ну смотрите
again, here’s your military commander. It’s not just some
еще раз вот ваши военкор Это не просто
drunk who knows promises military correspondents
какой-то знает [__] сулит военкоры
that they are constantly at the front.
которые они постоянно на фронте Они что
from the start of the
воздушно-десантные войска от начала
special operation to the start of mobilization, the airborne troops
спецоперации до начала мобилизации
lost 40 50 percent of their
потеряли 40 50 процентов своего личного
personnel, how did it happen that the idea was not
состава как так получилось идея не
lost, only the composition
потерялись только состава
in which boilers I wonder, even that’s
в каких котлах мне интересно даже вот
interesting Maybe they lost the Kiev region
интересно Может там Киевской области
there Kherson in Kharkiv
потеряли там Херсонской в Харьковской
Zhytomyr in Sumy
Житомирской в Сумской
that mobilization came to do because  that
что пришла мобилизацию делать потому что
so many of your regular military men
сдохла столько ваших кадровых военных
died more of yours Damn, but how inside is that
сдохла ваших больше Блин а как внутри
on the basis of which you say that there are
вот на основании чего вы говорите что
more of ours
наших больше
She began to talk I’m not saying to
Она стала говорить Я не говорю пока
watch more I’m talking about a specific
больше смотреть Я вот говорю конкретный
fact
факт
now
теперь
your war correspondents are not just
ваши военный корреспонденты не просто
some leftist people war
какие-то левые люди военные
correspondents on  your official
корреспонденты на официальном вашем
television talk about losses up to 50
телевидении говорят о потерях до 50
p  percent
процентов
[ __ ] up yes industrial time it's not that you
[__] да промтайм это не то чтобы
know in Vladivostok
знаете во Владивостоке
so look Let's So we
так вот смотрите Давайте Так мы
start from this video we can't
отталкиваемся от этого видео мы не можем
compare more less I just don't
сравнить больше меньше я вот просто я не
say We have more you have more we can't
говорю У нас больше у вас больше мы не
compare it here's the fact yes that's yours
можем это сравнить вот факт да что ваша
Here  this super army somehow lost in
Вот это супер армия как-то потеряла в
Ukraine
Украине
only before the start of mobilization 50
только до начала мобилизации 50
percent
процентов
Where, where, stepping in the Kiev region, they
Где где наступив в Киевской области
attacked, they drove you out of Chernihiv in
наступили выгнали вас Черниговской в
Zhytomyr, then in the Kharkov region
Житомирской потом в Харьковской области
and in Donetsk, we occupied Liman until then in
и в Донецке Лиман заняли мы до потом в
Kherson, now a new offensive is being prepared
Херсонской сейчас готовится новое
for us, you attacked everywhere here  with an
наступление нам вы везде наступили вот с
interval of 2 we have how they are preparing an
интервалом 2 у нас как готовят готовят
offensive they are preparing they are preparing they are
наступление делают готовят готовят
doing the
делают
Kharkiv region your troops fled, advance
Харьковской области убежали ваши войска
further
наступайте дальше
we were advancing the Kharkov region
мы наступали Харьковской области
and now they give us even now here the tanks
а теперь нам дают еще сейчас вот танки
there Abrams leopards will be the next
там Абрамс леопарды будут следующие
offensive
наступление
Yes, everything is so
Да все так
if if you were driven out of the Kiev
если если вас прогнали с Киевской
Sumy region  in general, there
Сумской области когда вообще еще техники
was really no technology yet, and you were driven out of the
толком не было да вас прогнали с
Kharkov region  when a little bit of
Харьковской области когда немножко
equipment was driven out of the Kherson
техники был вас прогнали с Херсонской
region When there was already a little more equipment
области Когда уже чуть больше техники
now, let's all go Yes, we
было сейчас пойдем все пойдем Да у нас
already have everything mobilizes us all on
все уже у нас всех мобилизирует нас на
the street, they take everyone in short, really, we
улице уже всех берут короче вот реально
’ll overwhelm you shortly Abram by ourselves,
вот завалим вас короче Абрам самим всем
so look, it turns out that now  we have a
так смотри получается что теперь у нас
technological advantage that
технологическое преимущество нам дают
Western modern equipment gives us, the very same
западную современную технику те самые
Harmers Yes, which shoot at the bottom of the
хармерсы Да которые стреляют внизу
inaccessibility of your artillery,
недосягаемости вашей артиллерии вот
remember this is the Makeevka vocational school Yes, on New
помните это макеевская ПТУ Да в Новый
Year's Eve
год
they gathered all these morons like
собрали этих всех дебилов типа
mobilized
мобилизированных
shoot where, according to your dispositions, like
стреляйте куда по вашим располагам вот
this, assemble the Makeevka vocational school gathered on
так собрать макеевская ПТУ собрались в
New Year's Eve all there  500 people flew in
Новый год все там 500 человек прилетел
Haymozda survived there 10 or that’s all and
хаймозда выжила там 10 или что вот и все
so on for all these and then
и так дальше по всех этих а потом еще
where else you shoot at all of them First, according to the
куда стреляете вот по всем Сначала по
location of the projectile where you don’t want to
распологам по снаряд куда не хочешь
shoot, I’ll say even more We even
стрелять еще больше скажу Мы даже по
shoot in the Belgorod region, we used to
Белгородской области стреляет раньше
say all if you don’t let  God, something is there
говорили всю если не дай Бог что-то там
on the territory of Russia, someone will attack it
на территорию России кто-то нападет это
will be a nuclear threat  We all showed
будет ядерную угроза Все мы показали
the whole world that Russia is a goof state.
всему миру что Россия государство [__]
Look, we take the
Смотрите Мы берем безнаказанно по
Belgorod region with impunity, your governor
Белгородской области ваш губернатор
says that I watched two or three months
говорит что я вот еще два месяца или три
ago that from the start of the special operation,
назад смотрел Что от начала спецоперации
20 people died in the Belgorod region
20 человек погибло Белгородской области
from shelling and Putin cannot protect
от обстрела и Путин не может защитить
the Belgorod region, imagine this is
Белгородскую область представляете это
laughter  and a shame for the whole world from Laughter and
смех и позор для всего мира от Смех и
shame on us for you guys Well, look
позор нас для вас ребят Ну как Смотри
what for us We are cool, we will shell the
что для нас Мы крутые мы обстрелим
Belgorod region with impunity and that
Белгородскую область безнаказанно и что
you are very cool Japanese look badge it’s
Вы очень крутые японцы смотрят бляха это
possible to shell Russia
же можно обстреливать Россию
with impunity Americans wash it off you can
безнаказанно американцы смою можно
shell Russia with impunity and all the
обстрелить Россию безнаказанно и все
same Opa  Opa rush
таки Опа Опа Раша
now not shelling before the Belgorod
сейчас не обстреливать до Белгородская
region Kursk Voronezh shelling and
область курскую воронежскую обстреле и
that Russia is
что Россия
silent
молчит
opening the news there they shelled there
открываешь новости там обстреляли там
they shelled so tell Donetsk shelling the
обстреляли так вот скажите Донецк
Belgorod region
обстреливает Белгородская область
shelling
обстреливает
shelling shelling let me see the latest
обстреливают обстреле давайте я свежие
news  The
новости Сейчас посмотрим
Belgorod
был ваш сайт 11 февраля Белгородской
region was restless from the side of
области было неспокойно со стороны
Ukraine, the villages of Murom came under fire But
Украины под обстрел попали села Муром Но
this is Volzhanka Shchebekinskaya moss and then here we are
это Волжанка щебекинская мох и тогдаш
11 today we are talking 13 two
вот 11 сегодня мы с вами говорим 13 два
days ago
дня назад
one day ago another Belgorod
один день назад очередная Белгородской
region of the Russian Federation reported several
области РФ сообщили о нескольких
arrivals so the
прилётах так
Belgorod region was fruitlessly attacked two days ago
Белгородской области два дня назад
infrastructural
бесплодненько атаковали инфраструктурные
Here is a fresh one, just a fresh selection, we
Вот свежий вот прям свежая выборка
’ll fire at it, and Putin, as the Grand
обстрелим получается и Путин как Гранд
Constitution of the city of immunity to the
Конституции города неприкосновенности до
Russian Federation, sits and is silent
Российской Федерации сидит и молчит
Belgorod residents say Vova Putin send in
белгородцы говорят Вова Путин введи
troops,
войска
he began to
он начал
understand for himself Putin began Ukraine
для себя понять Путин начал Украина
shelled Donbass for 8 years Putin began
обстрелил 8 лет Донбасс Путин начал
his own defense of Donbass, as a result of
своего по защите Донбасса в результате
which Ukraine  began to shell Belgorod
чего Украина начала обстрелять Белгород
and Putin
и Путин
to protect Belgorod
защитить Белгород
when Putin when Putin starts
когда Путин когда Путин начнет
a special operation to protect Belgorod it does
спецоперацию по защите Белгорода может
n’t matter Belgorod  we’ve already
без разницы Белгород Можно безнаказанно
hollowed out the Belgorod region from there, so
Харьковской области оттуда петляли так
now we’ve already hollowed
теперь
you
стояли Под самым харьковым уже вас
out from there, now we are the Belgorod
оттуда выдолбили теперь мы Белгородскую
region, [ __ ]
область
we quietly
[__] мы потихонечку
ran away to the Belgorod region from the
вы убежали в Белгородскую область из
Kharkov region and we are calmly shelling you from the Kharkov region
Харьковской и мы с Харьковской вас
where you are
спокойно обстреливают то что Куда вы
going there you will calmly shoot at the elderly
идете там Вы спокойно отстрелите пожилым
houses and the elderly  here, look, we have been
домам и пожилым тут смотрите мы вот
shelling for 8 years No, we have
обстреливали 8 лет Да нет мы
been training in Donetsk Lugansk for eight
тренировались на Донецке Луганске восемь
years,
лет
we are so bad, we are bad, we
мы такие плохие мы плохие мы
shelled our own Donetsk And now we will
обстреливали Донецк свои А теперь мы
shell your Belgorod residential houses And you
обстрелим ваши Белгород дома жилые А вы
Putin can’t do anything, well, it’s a
Путин ничего не может сделать ну-ка это
shame the whole world is watching that Russia
позор весь мир смотрит что Россию
some small state is shelling residential buildings
обстреливают жилые дома какая-то
[music]
[музыка]
Glad Glad
Рад Рад
You're not happy, I'm not Glad, because
А вы не рады что-то я не Рад потому что
I'm going to read it now, damn it, and it won't
я сейчас тоже прочитаю [__] и этого не
happen Let's read the spacebar, google
будет Давай прочитай пробелгород нагугли
the shelling of the Belgorod region,
обстрел Белгородская область
I won't be able to do
я сейчас не смогу
fresh news right now  it turns out
свежие свежие новости и все получается
look the whole world imagine that
смотри весь мир представляете чтобы
some kind of Mexico fired for example
какая-то Мексика обстреляла например
Just
Просто
if Mexico obs  chimed California what
если Мексика обстреливала Калифорнию что
would happen with mexico
было бы с мексикой
with mexico Yes Mexico won I think the
с мексикой Да Мексика победила Я думаю
USA would have wiped out all of these from the face of the earth
США об этом все стерло бы с лица земли
And here it turns out look and here the whole world I
А тут получается смотрите а тут весь мир
look Here it turns out America
смотрю Вот получается вот Америка
Where we didn’t go where she didn’t
Куда нам не заходила куда она не
[ __ ] come to Victory
приходила [__] никогда на Победу
she never [ __ ] went to Afghanistan didn’t
что-то она блин зашла в Афганистан не
annex Afghanistan to herself verak didn’t
присоединила себе Афганистан верак не
annex rocket suckers like it was necessary to
присоединила ракета лохи типа надо можно
hold a referendum crayfish
было референдуме раки провести
to annex the state
присоединить штатом
now only in Russia don’t wear [ __ ]
сейчас только в России [__] не
It was they who forced Putin to
Именно они заставили Путина на нас
attack us before We quarreled
напасть до Мы поссорились
we lived amicably with the Russians Americans  They
мы жили дружно с россиянами американцы
gave Putin money, like
Путина дали ему видно денежек типа
attack Ukraine, he attacked And now they
напади на Украину он напал А теперь они
give us Tanks Yes, so that we fall out
нам дают Танки Да чтобы мы вывалилась
everything is cool, you see in American Yes,
все круто видите по американски Да а
Putin doesn’t understand, he’s so sucker
Путин не понимает он настолько [__]
Belgorod region is shelling,
Белгородская область обстреливает
he is silent attacked your guys here We
он молчит напал сюда ваших ребят Вот
saw these videos at an angle for nothing  how many of
видели эти видео под угле даром сколько
your columns are dying you have seen
умирает ваших колонн видели
or shown
или показать
there you can google there by the corner of the
там можете нагуглить там по угле дар
gift  now the whole world is watching and just
сейчас уже весь мир смотрит и просто
now I’ll show you that is, when it
сейчас я вам покажу то есть когда это
was a year ago
было еще год назад
since I threw it off look while google
так как я скинул он смотрите пока
Damn if you know how or Yandex
загуглите Блин если умеете или яндекс
there what you have defeat under the corner for nothing
там чего у вас есть разгром под угле
let’s see in one day Alex
даром посмотрим за один день Алекс
counted in only one  in the episode of the battle 31,
насчитал в одном только эпизоде битвы 31
your wrecked equipment, they break so
подбитая техника ваша они ломятся так
our columns stupidly. In short, they will fire at their
колонны наши тупо Короче обстрелит их
arts like and
арты типа и
war is a war,
война это война
just the Americans there are also in shock.
просто американцы там тоже в шоке Почему
-there are
Вот но они все погибают но почему-то
no such
нету таких
videos from the Ukrainian side Yes, what, like the
видео с украинской стороны Да что типа
Ukrainian column goes and just like that
украинская колонна идет и вот так прям
breaks the whole column And we have a bunch of
всю колонну разбивает А у нас куча есть
such Yes, how we broke you
такое Да как мы вас разбивали
Well, because we don’t have
Ну потому что у нас нет
a video, damn it, we’re forbidden not to eat
видео блин нам запрещено не так есть
your drones, too, something  then they
ваши беспилотники тоже что-то снимают
just shoot something very little and somehow
просто что-то очень мало и как-то
unconvincing Well, nothing quietly,
неубедительно Ну ничего потихонечку вот
look here. The fact is that when Russia a year
смотрите Дело в том что когда Россия год
ago unexpectedly attacked Ukraine with a
назад неожиданно напала на Украину
huge mass and nothing  I could
огромной массой и ничего не смогла
do it, but now it turns out that they gave us
сделать а сейчас Получается нам надавали
American equipment, they still give us Yes, and what do you
американской техники еще дают Да еще еще
think, and I’ll kill them
как вы думаете
a little Yes,
и эти перебью немножко Да
when we drove into the storm Our troops
вот когда бучу заехали до Наши войска
Here it was to launch the dick Well, they
Вот она хуях было запускать
couldn’t hold the line of defense until
Ну не могли удержать линию обороны до
ours
нашей
retreated at the turn Yes, on which they could
отошли на рубеже Да на которых могли
defend  they came to [ __ ] and destroyed
обороняться приехали [__] и разровили
all the houses people lived there Now look, and
все дома люди жили там Теперь смотрите а
now they
теперь
regrouped and knocked you out Let's
перегруппировались и выбили вас Давайте
you don't want to hear me Let's why
ты не хочешь меня слышать Давайте зачем
they launched them who they were on the street of our
их запустили туда кого их по улице нашей
troops launched So they
войска запустили Вот и по улице их
were torn apart along the street not only Our
раздербанили раздербанили не только Наши
troops but people there  lived
войска но там же люди жили
if your troops are fighting there, you
если там ваши войска идут боевые
need to divide them
действия надо разделить
in the streets, you need to be all super, these columns
на улицах надо вас все супер эти колонны
of yours are burned, it’s just
ваши сожжены это просто
super about your people, we think if
супер о своих людях мы думаем если бы не
our people didn’t fit in, we would be alive Yes, we
влезли наши люди были бы живы Да мы
understand that during the fighting
понимаем что во время боевых действий
here in Stalingrad, remember the battle for
вот Сталинграде помните битва за
Stalingrad how many houses were destroyed
Сталинград сколько было разрушены домов
was why Stalingrad was allowed to the
было почему Сталинград допустили в
Germans in Stalingrad
Сталинград немцев
the battle was
битва была такая
so  you understand that
понимаете что вам
you couldn’t do anything a year ago And now with
год назад вы ничего не смогли А теперь
American and European weapons
американским и европейским вооружением
we can do even more here for 12
мы сможем здесь еще больше для 12
so the Russian Federation Glory to Ukraine
так Российской Федерации Слава Украине
Let the
Давайте
little man get tired that he was so sad Yes
подустал мужичок что он так загрустил Да
I love Tim cops
я люблю Тима менты Подписывайтесь Слава